

kevintravis120@gmail.com

O Kowloon, Hong Kong

+8616793468249

Profile

I am an entrepreneurial software engineer heavily focusing on web development as a Full-stack.

My focus is to help clients with their business by fixing and creating projects of value.

I have experience working as an individual developer and a project manager in many projects providing me with the skills of communicating with clients to satisfy their needs.

My experience tells everybody who I am, what I can do for your project.

A day in my life may consist of: prepping web art, fixing some front-end bugs, adding an API endpoint, dockerizing an application, database design, configuring a unit or UI test library, setting up a build or deployment plan, provisioning a test tier machine or feature work when I am lucky.

Employment History

Senior Full Stack Developer (Vue.js/Nuxt.js and Laravel), Brewly, San Carlos, California, United States

February 2021 — May 2021

In this position, I am now making the project side with Vue.js and Laravel, also, I am making the project Front-end side with Nuxt.js, too.

I am using

- · various npm libraries and making it.
- so many vendors and products for foods.

How it works-

- making real-time communication between users and admin.
- reviewing each product.
- shipping and good delivering any location.

Deployed Site URL

- https://brewly.io/

Frontend Developer (Nuxt.js), BBE Creative, Collingwood, Victoria

April 2020 — May 2021

This project was a small static sever-side-rendering website project that reworked their official website (their original official website is at the provided link).

• In this project, I set up and bootstrapped a project, determined the tech stack to be used, designed the project architecture, handled the development and deployment, and wrote detailed documentation.

Details

Kowloon Hong Kong +8616793468249

kevintravis120@gmail.com

Nationality

Hong Kong

Date of birth

1994/01/20

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Portfolio

Skills

Vue.js(Vue2 and 3), Nuxt.js, Vuetify, Vuex

React.js(Gatsby, Next.js), Redux (Saga and Thunk), Mobx

Backend Development (Laravel, Node, Express, GraphQL(Apollo, Hasura), Python/Django)

API Integration (Google Maps API, Chargebee, Activecampaign, Weather API)

REST API development

CMS (WordPress, Shopify, Drupal)

- I used Nuxt.js to develop the website and also introduced Typescript, and Vue-property-decorator to help improve the coding and development experience and quality.
- In addition, I also leveraged libraries such as moment, Vuex, Vue i18n, and Sass to achieve desired features from my client.
- I broke down the design into specific and reusable Vue.js components, and made them data-driven, which means data is separated into a corresponding JavaScript file and could be later easily replaced/hooked with the client's CMS back end.
- During the entire engagement, I communicated with my client every day to sync my progress as well as asking questions in the early stages.

Deployed Site URL

https://bbe.io/

Senior Full Stack Developer (MEVN), Group 166 Investment Fund LP, Seattle, WA, United States

August 2020 — January 2021

In this position, I've worked on Tax and Business visualization web app for Government.

Developing the US Government Platform:

- University and Company of the United States,
- · Calculating the Tax,
- Statistics the population
- etc...

Made with:

- Nuxt.js (Front-end)
- Node.js and Express.js (Back-end)
- MongoDB (Real-time Database)

I used the below techs:

- Google Maps API for showing each polygon details and drawing the polygons,
- Google Map Auto-complete for searching the location,
- Vue-Carousel Plugin for the slideshow of some pages, Vue-JSON-excel Plugin for downloading the CSV file, Bootstrap-Vue
- Typescript, Sass,
- Font-Awesome, Google Font API
- Alertifyjs for showing smart alert

Deployed Site URL:

https://oz-opportunity.herokuapp.com

Full Stack Developer, Upwork, Seattle, WA, United States

June 2020 — January 2021

- PHP/MySQL, Node.js Developer on a Social Networking Site: Me-vamping payment via Quaife method, Improvement user clicks 23% more than before using Coin merchant, Improvement Video/Audio Live Streaming with VIP rooms.
- Full Stack Development: Front-end (Vue.js: Nuxt/Vuetify/Vue3 (Composition API), React.js: Next/Gatsby/Redux (Saga and Thunk)/ Context API)
- Keeping good communication with clients, work more than 40 hrs per week.

UI Frameworks (Material Design, Anti Design, Element UI)

TypeScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS

Scrum / Agile Environments (GitHub, Bitbucket, GitLab, SVN, Jira, Trello)

Database (PostgreSQL, MongoDB, MySQL, Oracle)

Cloud Services (AWS, Azure, Firebase, Docker)

Hobbies

Coding Nice Web Art, Virtual Bug Hunting, Anything About JS, Exploring distant lands

Languages

English

Korean

Chinese

• Establish a good relationship with the teammates when developing the projects during working here.

Here are the previous working projects at Upwork:

- https://downeastcapital.com/
- 1. A SPA (single-page application) website for a private mortgage company.
- 2. It utilizes serverless hosting using AWS S3, CloudFront, Lambda, Route53, and SES.
- 3. It was developed using Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify.js, and Nuxt.js.
- https://smartmap.at/
- 1. I developed a production site analysis software for doctors.
- 2. After choosing a location, a doctor can see how many people live in the vicinity and other details about them.
- 3. The front end is built with Vue.js and the back end Node.js hosted on an EC2 instance. For the database, I used RDS with PostgreSQL.
- https://www.profipodnikatelskyplan.cz/
- PPP is a site for investors, who want to get their ideas validated. You can also find partners for potential business opportunities or invest in attractive business ideas.
- 2. I've worked on the front-end and CMS part of the site.
- https://dentalsleepsolutions.com/manage/
- I implemented several API endpoints using Laravel in a multiple-repository
 Docker project (micro-services), tested heavily with Selenium and PHPUnit (unit tests and integration tests).
- I migrated a great amount of PHP legacy code into a Vue.js single-page app using Vuex. I also took part in estimating tasks in the agile workflows as part of my role in the project.
- https://xiangqi-19724.herokuapp.com/
- 1. A complete JavaScript attempt of the popular Song dynasty board game.
- 2. The pieces and the graphics were rendered using SVG on the React framework and Node.js.
- 3. The AI moves were determined by examining and evaluating part or all of the subsequent options and finding the maximum of gains around these options.
- https://congwenma.github.io/memory_game/
- 1. A simple game that looks for two identical tiles at a time. The UI was built with React and MobX was used for state management.
- 2. And it was using Node.js and Typescript for Back-end.

Senior Frontend Developer (React.js), Perform Group, LLC®, York, Pennsylvania, United States

February 2020 — December 2021

- Designed the application architecture on TypeScript, React, and Redux.
- Designed a REST API with a subteam of back-end developers.
- Configured the project's Webpack build process.
- Led the front-end developers—doing code reviews to achieve maintainable and high-quality code.

- Worked in an agile scrum team.
- Created 27 web portals for the Football Federation in Australia, based on a custom dynamic template system.
- Built a front-end permissions library which became the company standard.
- Developed JavaScript sports widgets in an Agile distributed team.
- Created and improved graphical D3.js sports widgets—like pitches with positions and movements of players.
- Organized workshops for colleagues about Regular Expressions, Redux, and few smaller technical sessions.

Technologies: CSS3, Agile Software Development, Scrum, TypeScript, Redux, React, JavaScript, Web Development, Sass, D3.js, WebSockets, Webpack, PostCSS

Deployed Site URL:

http://www.performgroupllc.com/

Frontend Developer (React.js & RN), Hashletes, Culver City, California, United States

June 2018 — October 2020

- Implemented payment UI and API integration for both depositing funds and withdrawals.
- Added real-time multiplayer team lineups and membership status via Web Sockets (Firebase).
- Developed team details and invites UIs and API integration.
- Found and fixed various rendering performance issues in the app.
- Implemented app referral codes to give bonuses when a friend completes the process signup.

Technologies: Redux, React, JavaScript, iOS, Apollo, GraphQL, React Native

Full Stack Developer (Vue.js and Laravel), LessGo, Amman, Jordan January 2018 — June 2020

At my first Full Stack job, I was responsible for developing, implementing, and maintaining mostly internal web applications. I collaborated with technical and business staff in the design, development, testing, implementation, and production support of enterprise applications.

We primarily used Vue.js (Front-end) and Laravel (Back-end). 40% of my work was doing front-end development, 40% back-end development and the remaining 20% was dev-ops/sysadmin-related tasks.

We used the techs like:

- Google Maps API for drawing the route and calculating the distance between Starting and Arriving points.
- Google Firebase for verifying the email and phone number to register into the site.
- Socket.io for messenger between drivers and passengers.
- Various NPM modules for the Vue.js.

Deployed Site URL:

• https://www.lessgo.app/

WordPress Developer, 3PEAT, Los Angeles, California, United States

At 3PEAT, I was working on PHP-based services and applications.

Some of my web apps included: Digital menu boards, mobile/desktop business dashboards, online website plugins, and APIs.

I was also responsible for managing my team's web infrastructure, SEO, marketing, and website design.

I developed several popular websites like "God's Promise", "Skin Science"... with WordPress, Drupal here.

WordPress Developer, Sobold, London, England, United Kingdom *January* 2019 — *June* 2019

I worked as WordPress Developer as Part-time and made several products with WordPress.

Education

Bachelor's Degree, Science University of Tokyo, Bunkyo, Tokyo, Japan April 2011 — September 2015

I've learned below techs here:

- Front-end Development and Back-end Engineering (Full-Stack development).
- IT Technology
- Robotics scientist

Bachelor's Degree, University of Hong Kong, Pok Fu Lam, Hong Kong *January* 2016 — April 2018

After graduating from the University of Tokyo, I moved my next career into the University of Hong Kong,

Because it was also one of my dreams.

I learned a lot of IT technologies here.

References

Kevin Hansen from WeBase kvhproteam@gmail.com | + (852) 6619 5846